curvyclothing.com.au 2015-06-02

# Privacy & Return Policy | Curvy Clothing

Privacy Policy  
Privacy Statement for CurvyClothing.com.au CurvyClothing.com.au has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.curvyclothing.com.au

Return Policy  
We have 14 days Return policy, all items must be returned in their original condition, smoke and odor free or the items will be returned to you. (Sale and Bridal Merchandise are returnable for store credit only) 

Registration  
Our site's registration form requires users to give us customer contact information. We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company and to communicate order information. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.  
When you make a purchase on our site, you provide the following information to Curvy Clothing:

Name  
E-mail address  
Billing and shipping address  
Telephone Number  
Type of credit card you are using  
Credit card number and expiration date, or other form of payment  
Shipping preferences

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's financial information for the sole purpose of order processing. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. Cookies Simply put, a cookie is a small piece of information that web sites use to remember information about users. Curvy Clothing uses one type of cookie to recognize our members and remember shopping list items. Curvy Clothing uses transient cookies to provide continuity from page to page. Within a single visit, these cookies store information such as your shopping list to simplify checkout. They do not contain any personally identifying information. Curvy Clothing uses persistent cookies to identify members after their first visit. These cookies remain on the hard drive of a PC and allow a user to enter our site without having to log in on every visit. To access any secure areas such as your account information, you must still enter your login name and password. You can disable your cookies at any time through your browser options.

Choice/Opt-Out  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor. This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.  
You can send email to info@curvyclothing.com.au  
You can send mail to the following postal address:  
Curvy Clothing  
26 Rosa Cres  
Bracken Ridge QLD 4017

Correct/Update  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. Email info@curvyclothing.com.au Users can change/update account information prior to finalizing the checkout process. Data Sharing Curvy Clothing does not provide any third party with any individually identifiable information other than that which is necessary to complete your order. Specifically, Curvy Clothing gives your name, shipping address, phone number, and order information to our shipping carrier. We also supply your name, billing address, and credit card information to the credit card processor who bills your account. Curvy Clothing has strict guidelines requiring all third parties to keep any shared personal information confidential. If you have a question that is not answered here, please contact us and we will be happy to answer it for you. You can email us at info@curvyclothing.com.au

Contacting Curvy Clothing  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Website, you can contact:

Curvy Clothing  
26 Rosa Cres  
Bracken Ridge QLD 4017  
info@curvyclothing.com.au
